Preliminary Guide to the John C. Lilly papers M0786
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3. Conferences, workshops, catalogs, etc., 1980-1982
  - Crete Conference (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - U.C. Extension - Sept. 19, 1981 - Human Consciousness and Dolphins (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Washington University (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Series 4. Research files, by folder title [A-Z]
  - 4.1 "E" File - "N" File [incomplete]
    - "E" File (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "E" File (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - "F" File (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "G" File (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - "H" File (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - "I"/"J" File (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - "Ka-Ke" File (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - "Ke" File (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "Ki-Kz" File (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "L" File (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "L" File (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - "M" File (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "N" File (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - "N" File (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 4.2 Card catalog
    - Card catalog (authors, titles, subjects) (Flat-box 63)
    - Card catalog (authors, titles, subjects, "cogitate" test) (Flat-box 64)
    - Card catalog ("cogitate" test) (Flat-box 65)
    - Card catalog (contacts, publication distribution list) (Flat-box 66)
  - Altered States, lecture and film program (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesia for the Bottlenose Dolphin (E.J. Nagel, P.J. Morgan, W.L. McFarland), 1964 December (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Apple II Ops manual, 1979 January (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - John James Audubon, references to dolphins in his journals (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - AUI, Language of Space (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous B files (Box 42, Folders 5-8)
  - Basic Problems in Education for Responsibility caused by LSD-25, typescript, 1966 August 30 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous C files (Box 42, Folders 10-13)
  - Carbogen Experience (George N. Hazlehurst), 1974 August 6 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Cetacean bibliography (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Cetology, no. 35, 1979 December 31 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Characteristics, spectrograph, sonagraph, notes, 1964 January (Box 119, Volume 1)
  - Checks, circa 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folders 3-6)
  - Clippings, miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Co-directions, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Communication Between Man and Dolphin
    - Communication Between Man and Dolphin: The Possibilities of Talking to Another Species, typescript, circa 1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Communication Between Man and Dolphin: The Possibilities of Talking to Another Species, typescript, circa 1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Communication Between Man and Dolphin: The Possibilities of Talking to Another Species, typescript, circa 1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Communication Between Man and Dolphin: The Possibilities of Talking to Another Species, correspondence with publishers, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Communication between Man and Dolphin, galley proof (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Communications Research Institute
    - Communications Research Institute (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Communication Research Institute, audit reports, 1966 December (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Communication Research Institute, cartoon (Flat-box 61, Folder 1)
  - Conference on the Shark-Porpoise relationship, 1965 November 9 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Whale (Box 44, Folders 1-2)
  - Communication Research Institute, papers to be completed for publication, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Current Biography, vol. 23, no. 10; includes Lilly biography, 1962 November (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Cosmic Strip: Adventures of a Soul (Itzhak Bentov), 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Dictaphone word processors (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Discussion between Dr. Sidney Cohen and Dr. Lilly (on LSD), transcript of recording, 1967 February (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Dolphin Data Base, vol. 3, 1989 February (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Dolphins versus porpoises (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Dolphin’s Gift, galley proof (Elizabeth Gawain) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Dolphin’s Vocal Mimicry as a Unique Ability and a Step toward Understanding, typescript (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Dolphin’s Vocal Mimicry as a Unique Ability and a Step toward Understanding, galley proof (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Dow Corning Center for Aid to Medical Research (silicones) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - DYAD notes (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Earthtrust (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Ecosystem conference, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Education for Insight, Responsibility and Self Discipline, typescript, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Education projects (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Electrophysiological Investigation into Action of the Central Stimulant and Tranquillising Drugs (P. B. Bradley), 1961 May 31 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Esalen workshop, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Europe, 1983 May (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - European Forum for Human Sciences, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - An Experimental Investigation of Dolphin’s Communication abilities by Means of a Dolphin Machine Code, typescript (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Experiments Designed to find the Critical Thresholds for the Creation of Noise out of Intelligent Voice Signals, typescript, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Food and Agricultural Organization of the United Nations (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Future Presentations, 1980-1982 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - GamePro, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Germany workshop, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Hardcopy, Speaking with Dolphins, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Hubbs-Sea World Research Institute (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hubbs-Sea World Research Institute (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Human/Dimensions Institute West, workshop, 1981 March (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - The Human Bio-Computer: Programming and Metaprogramming with LSD-25, typescript, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Human/Dolphin Foundation
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, JANUS computer system, circa 1982 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, JANUS computer system, circa 1982 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, JANUS computer system, circa 1982 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, National Science Foundation proposal, circa 1980 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, personnel list (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, merchandise (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, miscellaneous materials (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, miscellaneous materials (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, miscellaneous bills (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, miscellaneous correspondence (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, report no. 4, 1980-1981 December-January (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, resumes (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, work/scholar program (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, work/scholar program (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Human/Dolphin Foundation, miscellaneous (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Humane Society (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - The Importance of Research on Interspecies Communication with Dolphins, typescript (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Injury and Excitation of Brain by Electrical Currents, typescript (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Human Behavior, conferences, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - International College, Los Angeles (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - International Dolphin Research Foundation (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - International Dolphin Society
    - International Dolphin Society (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - International Dolphin Society, reports and observations (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - International Dolphin Society, reports and observations (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - International Dolphin Society, reports and observations (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Human Consensus Reality as the Tranquilizer for Autonomy, lecture typescript (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Janus session (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Japan, circa 1992 (Box 60, Folders 5-7)
  - Japanese Magazines, 1993 (Box 47, Folders 7-9)
  - John C. Lilly Trust, account summaries, 1978 November (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Ketamine, cocaine, etc., and sexual response, test notes (Box 47, Folders 11-13)
  - Ladiat experiment, notes, 1968 June (Box 119, Volume 2)
  - Last Will and Testament, Richard C. Lilly (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - The Long Loneliness: Man and Porpoise: Two Solitary Destinies, reprint (Loren Eiseley), 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - LSD
    - LSD, Basic Problems caused by LSD-25, typescripts, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - LSD bibliographies, 1959-1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - LSD clippings (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - LSD clippings (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - LSD conference program, UC Berkeley, 1966 June (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - LSD, correspondence, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - LSD-25, mind-brain effects, lecture notes, 1966 November (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - LSD-25, therapeutic use, typescript, 1965 October (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - LSD articles, reprints (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - LSD articles, reprints (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - LSD articles, reprints (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - LSD articles, reprints (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - LSD articles, reprints (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - LSD, Theoretical Aspects of LSD Therapy, typescript (John Buckman), May 1965 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Magazines, miscellaneous (Box 116, Folders 10-11)
  - Man and Dolphin
    - Man and Dolphin, line copy (Flat-box 61, Folders 3-4)
    - Man and Dolphin, (London: Victor Gollancz LTD), with corrections by Lilly, circa 1962 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Man and Dolphin, review (Rhode Island Medical Journal), 1962 December (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Manuals
    - Manuals (Box 49, Folders 3-9)
    - Manuals (Box 50, Folders 1-11)
    - Manuals (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Mary Crouch Lilly versus John C. Lilly, divorce, 1978 February 6 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - M.D. workshop, 1973 December 8-9 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - M.D. workshop, 1974 February 16-17 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Military-Medico-Dental symposium, program, 1959 October (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Mind of the Dolphin, reviews, circa 1967-168 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Minigraph (Flat-box 62)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 51, Folders 6-8)
  - Miscellaneous organizations (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous reprints and articles (Box 51, Folders 10-16)
  - Miscellaneous reprints, scrapbook (Box 52, Folders 1-4)
  - Morgan, P.J., reprints (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - The Need for an Adequate Model of the Human End of the Interspecies Communication Program, typescripts, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - NOAA Technical Report, Whales, Dolphins, Porpoises of the Western North Atlantic, 1976 August (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Northern Kentucky University (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks, 1970 May (Box 52, Folders 8-9)
  - Orientation by means of Long Range Acoustic Signaling in Baleen Whales (Roger Payne and Douglas Web), reprint, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Outer and Inner Frontiers, typescript for presentation at the First International Symposium on Submarine and Space Medicine, 1958 September (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - PDP-11, manuals (Box 116, Folders 13-15, Box 117, Folders 1-3)
  - William L. Pensiger and Nha Trang Pensiger, story drafts (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Perception of Repeated Speech, notes, 1967 November 7 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Perception of Repeated Speech: Evocation and Programming of Alternate Words and Sentences, reprint, 1967 October 15 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Candace Pert, interview (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - PHP Institute International, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Piagetian Analysis of Dolphin Development (Nicholas Webb), 1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Poems (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Possibility of Intelligent Life Elsewhere in the Universe, Congressional report, November 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Problems of Basic Assumptions for Interspecies Communication, typescripts, circa 1965 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Project Interspeak (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Psychotherapy, typescript, circa 1966 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Report on work at St. Thomas and Sea Life Park, Oahu, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Reprints, miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Research ideas, notes (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - REST, conference, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Rights of Nonhuman Nature, conference, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Robots (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - RT-11, manuals (Box 117, Folders 4-9)
  - Russian periodicals, circa 1950-1975 (Box 118, Folders 2-5)
  - San Francisco Foundation, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Save the Dolphins (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Save the Whales (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Scientific Advisory Panel of the Biological Sciences Division, Air Force Office of Scientific Research, June 1959 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Scientific American, Medicine, vol. V, no. 8, August 1982 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Scientific American, Medicine, vol. V, no. 12, December 1982 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Scientific American, Medicine, vol. VI, no. 2, February 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Scientific Method applied to the Scientific Observer, miscellaneous typescripts, circa 1980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Second Conference on the Biology of Marine Mammals, December 1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Signal Processing (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Sierra Club (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Sociedad Mexicana para el Estudio de los Mamiferos Marinos, A.C. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Some Considerations of the Parameters of the Electrical Sub-Cortical Stimulation, typescript, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Some Observations on Body Flexibility of the Bottle-Nosed Dolphin (Frank S. Essapian), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Sonagram, notes (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Southern California Society of Clinical Hypnosis, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Special Considerations of Modified Agents, typescript (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University, seminar (E. Hilgard), July 1968 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Steps along the Way, chapters 9 and 11, typescript (Marie Dalloway) (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Sumitomo Corporation (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Symposium on Sensory Deprivation, program, June 1958 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Tank information (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Tiger trust (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - UCLA (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - University of Hawaii, seminar, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - University of Illinois, Department of Linguistics, lecture (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - University without Walls, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Vegetarian Life (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Warren, Richard M., reprints (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Water babies (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Whale bibliography (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Whale Center (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Whales, general information (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Whale Issue Committee (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Whale Museum, Friday Harbor, Wash. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Whale Protection Fund (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Who’s Who in the West (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Willard Water (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Windstar Foundation (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - World of Whales (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - World Sea Life (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - World Future Society (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Zapallar ("Quiet Zone") Experiment, March 20, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Series 5. Dolphin articles, reports, papers, etc.
  - Miami News 2/13/64 M/D Learn together (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Miami Herald 2/14/64 Dolphins teach to Lv (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Herald Tribune 8/2/64 - Earl Ubell article (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco Chronicle 11/24/64 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Island Times 8/14/59 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Daily News 9/19/59 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Alan Watts (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - N.Y. Times 1/16/65, 1/19/65 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Published Papers (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Underwater Birthing (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Who's Who (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Underwater Birthing 1981-82 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Lectures (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Newsweek Magazine (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Miami News 2/22/65 Keasler Column (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Publicity - JCL 1954-56 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Documents of Historical Interest (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Franklin Merrell Wolff (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Esalen (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Floatarium (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Dolphin's Vocal Mimicry as a Unique Ability and a Step Toward Understanding (Verbal Behavior Conf. - Sept. 1965) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Film Treatment (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - WUFF (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Current and Duplicates (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rest (Alma Daniels) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - R.E.S.T. Conference March 17/18 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Growth Centers (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Verbal Behavior Conf. Sept 1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Dolphin Vocalization - Conf. on Brain Mech. Under Speech & Lang., Princeton Nov.65 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Need for an Adequate Model of the Human End of the Interspecies Communication Program (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Start-Stop Systems (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - C.N.S. and Motivation, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Studies of the Bottlenose Dolphin, 1958-1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dolphins, Telepathy and Underwater Birthing (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Design 25, Dec. 6, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Dolphins Challenge the Designer (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dolphin Emotions Profile Index (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Series 6. Dolphin Repeated Word experiments
  - Final Draft - Perception of Repeated Speech: Evocation and Programming of Alternate Words and Sentences (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Rough Draft - Perception of Repeated Speech: Evocation and Programming of Alternate Words and Sentences (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Perception of Repeated Speech, CRI.1067, Evoc. & Prog. of Alternate Words & Sent. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Repeating Word File (Vault Office) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Frequency (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Repeated Speech and Projected Program Stem. Mono and Polysyllabic Words and Pairs (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Repeated Word-Sentence 10-20-67 (Rough Draft) Brain-Mind Model (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Human Bicomputer 10-20-67 Repeated Word-Sentence Exp. Brain-Mind Model 1st Copy (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Communication Research Institute (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Repeated Word Experiment (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Galley and original for Kopy Kat Reprogramming Sonic Output of Bottlenose Dolphin (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Reprogramming of the Sonic Output of the Dolphin (Box 27, Folders 3-4)
  - Sonic Burst-Count Matching (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sonic Burst-Count Matching (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Final Draft of Manuscript 5 copies (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Records (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp., master list of stimuli, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Test #4
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #4 Stim: "Kettle", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #4 Stim: "Kettle", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #4 Stim: "Kettle", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #4 Stim: "Kettle", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Test #5
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #5 Stim: "Punsuck", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Test #6
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #6 Stim: "Cat", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Test #7
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #7 Stim: "Kettul", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #7 Stim: "Kettul", October 1967 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Test #10
    - Repeated Word-Sentence Exp. (Rm. 42) Test #10: Stim. "Bravo" 201067 Subj. 091067 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Rm. 42) Test #10: Stim. "Bravo" 201067 Subj. 091067-A (orig) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Rm. 42) Test #10: Stim. "Bravo" 201067 Subj. 091067-A (copy) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #10 Stim: "Bravo", 1967 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Test #11 and 11/4
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #11 Stim: "Genital" 0211167 Subj. A. M. Miller (0910 67A) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #11 Stim: "Genital" 021167 Subj. J. C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #11 Stim: "Genital" 021167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Tests #11 & 4 Stim: "Genital" 021167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #11 Stim: "Genital" 021167 Subj. A. M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp.Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #11 & 4 Stim: "Genital" 021167A Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Tests #11 & 4 Stim: "Genital" 021167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Tests #11 & 4 "Genital" 021167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Test #12
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 A Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj: A.M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 A Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 A Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 A Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 B Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 B Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 B Stim. "God loves you" 031167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #12 B Stim: "God loves you" 031167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Test #13
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #13 Stim: "Deeper and Deeper" 031167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. 031167 Test #13 Stim: "Deeper and Deeper" Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Test #14
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #14 Stim: "ABCDEHI" 021167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #14 Stim: "ABCDEHI" 021167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #14 Stim: "ABCDEHI" 021167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #14 Stim: "ABCDEHI" 021167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Test #15
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #15 Stim. "Battling" (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Test #16
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #16 Stim. "Bravo" (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Test #17
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #17 Stim. "Trapped" (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. A.M. Miller (091067A) (Copy) (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. Ernst Rothauser Ph.D. (111167-1) orig (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. Ernst Rothauser Ph.D(111167-1)copy (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. W.W. Lang, Ph.D.(111167-2) orig (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. W.W. Lang, Ph.D. (111167-2) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. G.E. Urbanek, Ph.D. (111167-3) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 45)